jquery-az.com 2019-08-08

# Cookies and Privacy Policy

### Cookie and Privacy Policy of jQuery-az.com

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?**

jquery-az.com do not collect information from visitors of our site. We only provide information articles, tutorials, tips and tricks that do not require any personal information from the user.

A few demos may include forms with textboxes, however, these are for only demo and any dummy information can be entered for testing prupose.

This information is not saved in any form.

### **How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We do not use Malware Scanning.

We use an SSL certificate

**•** We only provide articles and information, we never ask for personal or private information like email addresses, or credit card numbers.

### **Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**We use Cookies for:**

Improving our website for speed and better user experience.

**Cookies are not used for:**

  * Any shopping carts
  * passing any personal identifiable information to third parties.
  * Pay sales commissions.

### **Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise, transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

### Usage of Statistical Cookies

We use Google Analytics which is owned by Google ([privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/)) for:

  * Knowing how many people have visited the website.
  * Users technologies like Operating System, Browser type, duration of a visit, page views etc.
  * Knowing the source of traffic e.g. Search Engines like Google, Bing, Yahoo, Social Networks (Facebook, Twitter etc.)

You may read the privacy policy of Google Analytics by following above provided link.

### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### **Google adsense(Advertisement)**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

### **We have implemented the following:**

**•** Remarketing with Google AdSense

**•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiativeoptoutpage or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### **How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### **Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we do not allow third party behavioral tracking

### **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

### **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via in site notification

**•** Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at info@jquery-az.com**

and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information in the [contact page](https://www.jquery-az.com/contact/).
